Alumni Memorabilia; Collection ua801.004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Class of 1967, 1962-1969; 1967
  - Special Activities and Events, 1962-1969; 1967.2
    - Uptown Campus and Colonial Quad Construction Photographs, 1967 March-1967 July (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 22)
    - Class Trip to Expo '67 Photographs, 1967 June 05-1967 June 07 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 23)
    - Senior Week Events Tickets, Programs, and Procedures, 1967 June 05-1967 June 11 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 24)
    - Alumni Council Annual Meeting and Dinner Program, 1967 June 09 (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 25)
    - Class of 1967 Commencement Photographs, 1967 June (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 26)
    - Class of 1967 Senior Week Cocktail Mixer and Stirrer, 1967 June (Artifact-box 1)
    - Class of 1967 Senior Week Matchbooks, 1967 June (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 27)
    - Class of 1967 Torch Night Candle, 1967 June (Artifact-box 2)
    - Class of 1967 Torch Night Photographs, 1967 June (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 28)
    - Senior Gala Photographs, 1967 June (Box 2 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 29)
    - Senior Week Event Photographs, 1967 June (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 1)
    - Senior Week in the Dorms Photographs, 1967 June (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 2)
    - Senior Week Posters, 1967 June (Oversized 4, Folder 2)
    - The Word, 1967 November (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 3)
    - Alumni Association Handbook, 1967 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 4)
    - Campus Viewpoint, 1967 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 5)
    - Draper Campus Photographs, 1967 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 6)
    - Torch Yearbook, 1967 (Oversized 1)
    - Minerva Move From Library to Uptown Campus Photographs, ca. 1967 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 7)
    - Minerva Restoration Photographs, ca. 1967 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 8)
    - Minerva Rededication Speech, ca. 1967 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 9)
    - Primer, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 10)
    - Primer Anthology, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 11)
    - Student Guidelines, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 12)
    - The Word, 1968 February (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 13)
    - Big Prints Exhibition Catalog, 1968 February 16-1968 March 18 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 14)
    - Observation, 1968 Spring (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 15)
    - Psi Gamma 70th Anniversary Jug, 1968 March 30 (Artifact-box 3)
    - Psi Gamma 70th Anniversary Mementos, 1968 March 30 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 16)
    - The Word, 1968 Fall (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 17)
    - Campus Viewpoint, 1968 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 18)
    - Primer, 1969 Spring (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 19)
    - Campus Viewpoint, 1969 (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 20)
    - Alpha Phi Gamma Kappa Chapter Stationery, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 21)
    - Alumni Hall Construction Site Negatives, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 22)
    - Anonymous Class of 1967 Student Photograph, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 23)
    - Campus Center Student Government Office Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 24)
    - Class of 1967 Beanie Photocopy, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 25)
    - Class of 1967 Class Member Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 26)
    - Class of 1967 Stationery, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 27)
    - Draper Campus Photograph, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 28)
    - Homecoming Against Potsdam Parade Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 29)
    - Homecoming Against Plattsburgh Parade Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 30)
    - Mementos, Including Stamps and a Button, Undated (Artifact-box 2)
    - President's Reception Invitation, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 31)
    - Print of Uptown Campus Painting by S.F. San Pedro, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    - Set of Five University Campus Watercolors by Davis Gray, Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 3-7)
    - Student Organization of Services Booklet, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 32)
    - Summer Re-Cataloging Project at Hawley Hall Photograph, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 33)
    - Willett Street Normal School Photograph, Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 8)
    - Willett Street State Normal School Clipping, Undated (Box 3 (1967-Class of 1967), Folder 34)
- Class of 1975
  - Great Dane Football Program Albany vs. Norwich, 1975 October 25
  - Texas License plate, "SUNYA" donated by David P. Taffet '75, 1981 March 28
  - Hal's Campaign, partial script, ca. 1975
  - Various unidentified photographs, ca. 1975